{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Floating Dock Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/62556/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62556,"taskName":"Floating Dock - Build","taskDescription":"Build a Floating Dock","xmTaskDescriptor":"Floating Dock Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Water Dock construction Build jetty floating boat","textMessagingName":"Build Floating Dock","rolloverLongDesc":"May involve wood, concrete, plastic \u0026 composite building materials. Includes boat houses, ramps, swimming platforms, berths, boat cranes \u0026 all other waterfront installations.","rolloverShortDesc":"Build or replace floating waterfront structure.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Build a Floating Boat Dock or Jetty.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area.","htmlTitle":"Floating Dock Builders \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install a Floating Dock or Jetty","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":21,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Floating Dock Build","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Floating Dock - Build","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Floating Dock Project","urlName":"Floating-Dock-Build","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Floating Dock Builders in \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Floating Dock Installation","searchKeywords":"Water Dock construction Build jetty floating boat","emcCategoryOid":-12023,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":9199,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62556/":{"taskOID":62556,"originalTaskOID":62556,"setID":9199,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4828,"questionDisplayText":"Dock Size Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What size dock do you need? (in square feet)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200780,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Small (Less than 100 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Small (Less than 100 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200781,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Medium (100 - 200 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Medium (100 - 200 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200782,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Large (Greater than 200 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Large (Greater than 200 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4830,"questionDisplayText":"Water Conditions","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What are the conditions where the dock will be installed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3440,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lake","answerDisplayText":"Lake","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5362,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"River","answerDisplayText":"River","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4326,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Ocean","answerDisplayText":"Ocean","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Strong current","answerDisplayText":"Strong current","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1864,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Deep water (10+ feet)","answerDisplayText":"Deep water (10+ feet)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3719,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Major tide changes (5-10+ feet)","answerDisplayText":"Major tide changes (5-10+ feet)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5850,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Soft bottom","answerDisplayText":"Soft bottom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5371,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Rocky bottom","answerDisplayText":"Rocky bottom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5482,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Sandy bottom","answerDisplayText":"Sandy bottom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":70000,"questionDisplayText":"Financing Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need financing?","shortQuestionText":"Do you need financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4828,"questionDisplayText":"Dock Size Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What size dock do you need? (in square feet)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200780,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Small (Less than 100 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Small (Less than 100 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200781,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Medium (100 - 200 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Medium (100 - 200 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200782,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Large (Greater than 200 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Large (Greater than 200 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200780,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Small (Less than 100 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Small (Less than 100 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200781,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Medium (100 - 200 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Medium (100 - 200 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200782,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Large (Greater than 200 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Large (Greater than 200 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4830,"questionDisplayText":"Water Conditions","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What are the conditions where the dock will be installed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3440,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lake","answerDisplayText":"Lake","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5362,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"River","answerDisplayText":"River","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4326,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Ocean","answerDisplayText":"Ocean","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Strong current","answerDisplayText":"Strong current","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1864,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Deep water (10+ feet)","answerDisplayText":"Deep water (10+ feet)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3719,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Major tide changes (5-10+ feet)","answerDisplayText":"Major tide changes (5-10+ feet)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5850,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Soft bottom","answerDisplayText":"Soft bottom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5371,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Rocky bottom","answerDisplayText":"Rocky bottom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5482,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Sandy bottom","answerDisplayText":"Sandy bottom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3440,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lake","answerDisplayText":"Lake","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5362,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"River","answerDisplayText":"River","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4326,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Ocean","answerDisplayText":"Ocean","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Strong current","answerDisplayText":"Strong current","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1864,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Deep water (10+ feet)","answerDisplayText":"Deep water (10+ feet)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3719,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Major tide changes (5-10+ feet)","answerDisplayText":"Major tide changes (5-10+ feet)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5850,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Soft bottom","answerDisplayText":"Soft bottom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5371,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Rocky bottom","answerDisplayText":"Rocky bottom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5482,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Sandy bottom","answerDisplayText":"Sandy bottom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":70000,"questionDisplayText":"Financing Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need financing?","shortQuestionText":"Do you need financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}